## OLALEYE ADEDAYO OREOLUWA

BIODATA	Date of birth: 15 <sup>th</sup> November 1993 Sex: Male Nationality: Nigerian	
OBJECTIVE	I am a Software Developer with first class communication skills with an urge for knowledge and experience. Inquisitive developer with over 2+ years of developing experience and looking to leverage more strong skills in Technological development	f
TECHNICAL SKILLS	JAVA	%100
JIVIELO	SQL DATABASE	
	SPRING FRAMEWORK	
	HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP	
	JAVASCRIPT	
	PYTHON	
	SERVER MANAGEMENT	

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### LONGBRIDGE TECHNOLOGIES (SOFTWARE ENGINEER) OCT 2019 – PRESENT

- Building Restful web-services using SPRING BOOT for both WEB and MOBILE application
- Application support on several client applications using PLAY FRAMEWORK
- Managing application and web server on Ubuntu
- Developing full-stack web application using THYMELEAF or JSP with spring
- Support existing applications for client

## SUPERSOFT TECHNOLOGY LIMITED (WEB APPLICATION/SOFTWARE DEVELOPER) JANUARY 2019 – OCTOBER 2019

- Design, develop and support web-based applications using SPRING FRAMEWORK (SPRING-BOOT & SPRING MVC)
- Operate in line with testing plans and procedures in developing and testing software.
- Developing front-end interface using HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT.
- Creating and updating database using MySQL.
- Ensure every required security (standard and proprietary) is implemented on all applications and system to be developed by the organization.

## MINISTRY OF FINANCE (NYSC – I.T CONSULTANT JANUARY 2015 – OCTOBER 2015)

- -System Troubleshooting and repairs
- Network Management
- Making recommendations such as suggesting appropriate hardware, software applications.
- Giving staff computer training

# OMATEK COMPUTERS LIMITED (INDUSTRIAL ATTACHMENT JANUARY 2013 – SEPTEMBER 2013)

#### HARDWARE ANALYST

- Desktop hardware assembly and configuration in laboratory.
- System hardware diagnostics.
- Installations of operating systems
- Installation of different computer software applications
- System hardware troubleshooting

COMPLETED PROJECTS	<ul> <li>SCHOOL MANAGEMENT SYSTEM (S.M.S)         This is a management system for majorly HIGH and BASIC schools, a system with 3 different interface which are the school as ADMIN. the teachers and parents, I built this using SPRING BOOT FRAMEWORK.     </li> <li>Incidence Management System (I.M.S)         This is an enterprise application majorly for organizations providing a service, this platform acts as a support manager and collects complains, comments, reports from all customers and gives the firm a platform to respond, I built this using SPRING MVC FRAMEWORK.     </li> <li>DIGITAL ATTENDANCE SOLUTION {D.A.S}         This is a MOBILE application with a WEB admin interface, this application is used as a clock in &amp; out system using the users geofencing with a face verification on users mobile phone, application is used to generate hours of work, attendance and get user's locations.     </li> </ul>
EDUCATION	
LDUCATION	HOME SCIENCE ASSOCIATION SECONDARY SCHOOL (2004 – 2010) S.S.C.E / W.A.E.C
	BOWEN UNIVERSITY IWO OSUN STATE (2010 – 2014) Bachelor of Computer Science (Information Technology) Second Class Honors (Lower Division)
TRAININGS	
	- ORACLE SQL DATABASE (ORACLE 11g CERTIFIED 2015)
	- DIPLOMA IN JAVA PROGRAMMING (NIIT)
	- DIPLOMA IN WEB DEVELOPMENT (HTML5, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP, CSS)(NIIT)
	- NYSC DISCHARGE CERTIFICATE (2014 – 2015)